This is your time, right now be ready.
If there is any area of your life God has not touched,
our Lord Jesus Christ is concerned about you.
He loves you just like any of His apostles.
Hallelujah!
Are you ready?
Right now bow down your head and give thanks to Him.
You have seen the name Jesus working in the spirit.
You have seen the anointing of God working in the spirit.
The power of God working in the Spirit.
Give thanks to Him.
What a God we serve, what a Son we have.
Father, thank You. Holy Spirit, thank You.
Hallelujah!
I can't hear you.
[Amen.]
This is the day the Lord has made.
I stretch my right hand.
The right hand of God is power.
Let the power of the Lord come down
From Heaven above
Where can you go from His presence?
[Nowhere!]
East, South, North, West?
Right now, whatever bondage that you are in, be released in the name of Jesus!
Right now, whatever bondage you are in,
take the authority of Jesus and begin to release yourself.
I release myself, in the name of Jesus!
I command that bondage to be broken!
I command that cage to be opened!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Take the authority of Jesus Christ
and begin to release yourself from whatever bondage you are in.
Open that cage - cage of generational curses!
Open it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I open every cage of generational curses!
Be opened, in the name of Jesus!
Every cage of generational curses - be opened!
You know you are not here for yourself alone, you are here for your family, community, nation
and for the whole world.
There are nations that have been caged.
There are communities that have been caged.
There are continents that have been caged.
Right now, open your lips and begin to open every cage of generational curses.
Begin to open it right now, in the name of Jesus!
Open it, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
There are lives that are in a cage.
There are businesses that are in a cage,
finances that are in a cage, marriages that are in a cage,
careers that are in a cage.
Every cage of generational curses - begin to open it right now and walk out of it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I command your health to be restored!
That pain in your blood, kidneys, liver, tendons, muscles, bones,
command them out!
Open your lips and begin to command them out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Viewer all over the world, begin to command that pain!
Viewers all over the world, begin to command that pain in your bones, muscles, liver, kidneys,
blood, fluids, tendons.
Begin to command them out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Your faculties, I mean your system - your bones, kidney, liver, blood, tendons -
wherever in your system, it must listen to the voice of God.
I say, listen! Wherever the pain in your system is - be it in your womb, kidneys,
liver, blood - I say, out!
You fibroid - I say, out!
Command them out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever you might have eaten in your dreams,
whatever you might have eaten from the table of your enemies,
right now, begin to purge it, by the blood of Jesus!
By the blood of Jesus and the power of the Holy Ghost, I purge it out!
Say, out!
Begin to purge it out!
By the blood of Jesus, by the power of the Holy Ghost,
whatever I might have eaten from the table of my enemies, in my dreams, I purge it out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Listen to me.
Whatever you might have eaten knowingly or unknowingly
from the table of your enemy or in your dreams,
begin to purge it out in the name of Jesus!
By the blood of Jesus, purge it out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Viewers all over the world,
whatever you might have eaten knowingly or unknowingly
from the table of your enemy or in your dreams,
be removed! Be delivered!
Believe Jesus for your delivarance
I say, this is the day that you have been praying for.
I say, be delivered!
By the blood of Jesus, be purged, in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Give thanks to God- Rejoice!
Right now, commit your career, finances, business into the hands of God.
Commit your career. Cover your career with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your business with the blood of Jesus!
Cover your career with the blood of Jesus!
Cover them with the blood of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, begin to touch your business.
Touch your business by faith.
I touch you, my business. Whatever you touch shall be blessed.
You, my business, finances, career.
My hands are blessed
With the blessings of the Lord
Anything I touch
Surely must be blessed
My hands are filled
With the blessings of the Lord
My hands are blessed
Anything I touch
Surely must be blessed
My hands are filled
With the blessings of the Lord
I cover your career with the blood of Jesus!
Your business, your finances, your way be covered by the blood of Jesus!
Be secured!
Be covered by the blood of Jesus!
Give thanks to God.
Hallelujah.
Right now, your country, your nation.
Right now, bring the flag of your nation and wave it.
Begin to release your nation from whatever covenant -
generational covenant, whatever covenant your nation might have had,
begin to release your nation.
I release my nation, I release my country, I release my continent.
Release them from corruption, killing, stealing, destruction,
misappropriation and shedding innocent blood..
Release them.
Bless the Lord oh my soul
Oh my soul
Worship His holy name
Sing like never before
Oh my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
Bless the Lord oh my soul
Oh my soul
Worship His holy name
Sing like never before
Oh my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
Bless the Lord oh my soul
Oh my soul
Worship His holy name
Sing like never before
Oh my soul
I'll worship Your holy name
Open your lips and begin to release your nation from every covenant!
Whatever covenant - killing, stealing, destruction, corruption,
misappropriation, shedding innocent blood - release your nation!
Ask God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Viewers all over the world, pray for your nation, country.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Give thanks to God.
Hallelujah.
Give thanks to God for your nation.
Give thanks to God.
Open your lips.
Lord Jesus, I receive You into my life.
I believe that You save me now.
Thank You for Your salvation.
Give thanks to God.
Give thanks to Him.
Lord Jesus, I receive You into my life.
I believe that You save me now.
Thank You for Your salvation.
Hallelujah! Give thanks to God! Wave your hand!
Hallelujah! Give thanks to Him!
Give thanks to God!
Hallelujah!
It shall be permanent.
I am very sure as a prophet that the life you are taking home now
is not the same life that you came with.
Listen - the life you are taking home now is not the same life that you came with.
It shall be permanent.
I say to your business - it is a new dawn.
I say to your career - it is a new dawn.
I say to your finances - it is a new dawn.
I say to your health -, it is a new dawn.
I say to your marriage - it is a new dawn.
Good morning!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
I am telling you God's opinion.
The life you came with is not the same life you are going with.
You are an ex-loser.
I said, you are an ex-loser.
Do you know what I mean by that?
Ex-loser.
It shall be permanent!
Look.
The life you came with is not the same life you are going home with.
It means in your business - it is a new dawn.
To your career - it is a new dawn.
To your finances and health, in Jesus' name!
I am looking forward to your testimony.
Right now, begin to share your testimony.
It shall be permanent
What the Lord has done for me
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.